威尔 · 森坦斯: 所以我们现在要谈谈在 ES2015和
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So we are now going to
move onto what changed in the ES2015 and
全世界。
on world.
Es6世界。
The ES6 world.
所以在那之前，我们之前看到的。
So until then, what we saw here before.
这个模型，还记得我们这个漂亮的模型吗？
This model,
remember that beautiful model here we had?
差不多就是这样。
That was pretty much it.
然后承诺出现了，一切都变得有点不同了。
And then along came promises, and
everything got a little bit different.
它的前提是。
The premise for it is this.
如果我试着总结一下，前提是这样的。
If I were to try and sum it up,
the premise would be this.
当我有这个模型的时候，当我使用 setTimeout 的时候。
When I had this model here,
when I used setTimeout.
在 JavaScript 中做了什么吗？
Did setTimeout do anything in JavaScript?
没有结果是什么 Kayla？
No, where was its consequence, Kayla?
在网页浏览器里。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: In the web browser.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 在网页浏览器上，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: In the web browser,
spot-on.
但是一旦我在浏览器中设置好计时器,
But once I've set up
the timer in the web browser,
记录我已经开始使用它的事实，或者其他背景特征？
keeping track of the fact that I've
started it, or other background features?
我在 JavaScript 中没有找到任何方法来跟踪它，对吧？
I didn't really get any way of tracking
that back in JavaScript, right?
在 JavaScript 中，我只是把它们扔掉。
In JavaScript,
I kinda just threw them out.
现在，我可以使用我的控制台在 JavaScript 数据和 JavaScript 中使用 console.log 状态。
Now, I can console.log state In JavaScript
data and JavaScript using my console.
但是我不能去想象这里所有的东西。
But I can't go and visualize all
the stuff that was down here.
没有像控制台那样的可视化网页浏览器,
There's no like console visualize it for
the web browser,
这有点过时了，对吧？
which is that is a little bit old, right?
你所做的一半显然比你在 JavaScript 中所做的一半多
That half of what you're doing obviously
more than half what you do in JavaScript
正在这里发生。
is happening down here.
我得到了一种没有跟踪，它不能保持一致性
And I'm getting kind of no tracking of
it can no maintaining of consistency
我记忆中的数据
between the state,
the data I see up here in my memory and
这里发生的事情。
the stuff that's happening down here.
没有一种方法可以描绘出我在这里做什么
There's no kind of way of mapping
what I'm doing down here in
浏览器和这里发生的事情。
the web browser with what's
going on up here in JavaScript.
这是在开发者的推理和思考我们正在做什么的方面
That's in terms of developer reasoning and
thinking about what we're doing as we
然后去维护应用程序的规模，这并不是我想说的理想。
go and sort of maintaining the application
scale that isn't that ideal I would say.
我认为承诺绝对是最有价值的
And I would put promises as
the absolute one of the most valuable
他们提供的作品，他们也有所有的好处，这是一个愿望说,
pieces they offer, they have all
the benefits as well, is a desire to say,
当你在背景里触发什么东西的时候，不要把它扔出去。
when you trigger something in the
background, don't just throw it out there.
但是它在 JavaScript 内存中也有某种结果。
But have it have some sort of consequence
in JavaScript memory as well.
所以，我有一个一致性之间的事情进行背景是要去
So, that I have a consistency between
things going on in background is gonna
在某种程度上对 Java 产生了一些影响。
have some consequence back
in Java at some point.
不知怎么的，我也在 JavaScript 内存中记录了这些信息。
And I'm somehow keeping track of that
within JavaScript memory as well.
在 ES6中，我们引入了我称之为双管齐下的 facade 函数。
So with ES6, we introduced what I'm
gonna call two-pronged facade functions.
他们不仅仅是，让我们记住我们的网络浏览器，里面有什么。
They did not just, let's remember
our web browser, what's in it.
我们有 JavaScript 引擎，JS，JavaScript 引擎,
We had our JavaScript engine,
we had our JS, our JavaScript engine,
我们还有很多浏览器功能,
and then we also had a ton
of browser features,
其中一个是对互联网的网络请求。
one of which was speaking to
the Internet the network request.
而且它的标签。
And that its label.
我们有一个老式的标签，这个标签的作用方式和设置暂停是一样的。
We have an old school label, that by the
way worked in the same way as set timeout.
添加了一个功能把它放到了网页浏览器里,
Took a function,
threw it down into the web browser,
设置一个老式的定时器。
set up a timer with the old school style.
我们有一个新的学校风格的设置浏览器功能对话互联网,
We have a new school style of setting up
the browser feature speak to the Internet,
跟推特聊聊，不管它是什么。
speak to Twitter, whatever it might be.
通过互联网发送更多数据请求。
Send a request for
more data over the Internet.
在 JavaScript 中，它的标签是 fetch。
And the label for
it in JavaScript is fetch.
但是有一种新的明星方式来做到这一点。
But there's a new star way of doing it.
这是一个双管齐下的门面函数。
It's one I'm gonna call it
two-pronged facade function.
它确实在网络上建立了一个网络请求
It does set up a network
request in the web
浏览器功能，我一直在做这个。
browser features, I keep doing that.
在 web 浏览器的特性中，它在这里设置了一个网络请求。
In the web browser features, it does
set up a network request down here.
但与其这么做然后什么都不做,
But rather than just doing that and
then nothing,
从那时起就没有办法知道这是用 JavaScript 完成的,
no way of knowing this being
done in JavaScript from then on,
这在 JavaScript 中也会立即产生结果。
it's gonna have a consequence
immediately in JavaScript as well.
这个获取标签会触发这里的互联网对话。
This fetch label is gonna trigger
speaking to the Internet down here.
发送网络请求，对互联网说话，请求
Sending a network request,
speaking to the internet, asking for
来自 Twitter 的数据。
data from Twitter down here.
同时在 JavaScript 中,
And simultaneously it's
going to also in JavaScript,
在 JavaScript land 中返回
in the JavaScript land return out
一种特殊的物体，叫做承诺物体。
a special kind of object
called a promise object.
这些都会留在记忆中。
That's going to sit in memory.
当背景工作在这里完成，这将填充和
And when the background work is done here,
that's going to fill in and
用背景中的数据更新对象的数据。
update that object's data with
the data from the background.
现在当我们完成背景工作后,
And now when we finish
our background work,
我们一点都不惊讶，有些东西会有结果
we are not surprised that something's
gonna have a result back in
因为我们有一个双管齐下的 facade 函数。
JavaScript because we had
a two pronged facade function.
它在这里产生了后果，一针见血。
It had consequences out here, one prong.
但是它在 JavaScript 中立即产生了另一个结果。
But it had another consequence
immediately in JavaScript.
一个小小的占位对象，可以让我们
A little sort of placeholder object
that's gonna allow us to keep
在我们的本地内存或者全局内存中追踪 JavaScript
track in JavaScript in our local memory or
in our global
我们在浏览器里触发的东西的记忆。
memory there of the stuff we triggered
off down here in the web browser.
所以现在我们有点像把这两个映射在一起，它们紧密地联系在一起。
So now we kinda have these two mapped
together and they're intimately linked.
后台特性在它完成时将对
The background feature when it completes
is going to have consequences for
然后立即返回 JavaScript 对象。
that immediately returned
down JavaScript object.
我们会看到它在这里发挥，但看看它,
We're gonna see it play through here,
but take a look at it,
双管齐下的外观功能，都启动后台网页浏览器工作
two pronged facade functions that both
initiate background web browser works
并返回一个位置持有者对象。
being the Internet and
return a place holder object.
这只是一个物体的电荷
It's just a charge of object but
一个特殊的类型，在 JavaScript 的世界里立刻就有了承诺。
a special type of one with a promise
immediately in JavaScript land.
这样我们就有办法确保我们知道下面发生了什么，因为
So that we have a way of making sure we
know what's going on down here because
我们一直在更新。
we've kept it up to date up here.
非常有趣，是一个非常有趣的概念。
Really interesting,
is very interesting concept.
我们开始吧。
So here we go.
我们要在这里看比赛。
We're gonna see it play out here.
保存一个函数显示，希望是要运行的数据
Save a function display, which hopefully
is gonna be run with the data that
从 Twitter 上得到的数据，然后我们就可以得到他的标签未来的数据。
comes back from Twitter as input, then
we're going to have his label future data.
然后在右手边,
And then on the right hand side there,
这个五个字母的单词是 JavaScript 中最强大的。
the five letter word that is
the most powerful in JavaScript.
这五个字母的作用是非常复杂的。
It is profoundly complex
what those five letters do.
他们准备开始与互联网对话。
They are going to set out
speaking to the Internet.
这个五个字母的字面意思是指互联网
That five letter word literally
speaks to the Internet down here from
网页浏览器。
the web browser.
不是在 JavaScript 中，JavaScript 不能做到，但是 web 浏览器可以。
Not in JavaScript, JavaScript can't do it,
but the web browser can.
这就是五个字母的单词的力量。
That is how powerful
that five letter word is.
它使用了大量的技术
It's using a myriad of
technologies to go and
从世界的另一端获取数据。
get data from the other side of
the world Adrian, JavaScript.
相信我，JavaScript 没有这个功能。
JavaScript does not have that feature,
believe me.
但是网页浏览器有着无数惊人的功能
But the web browser has
a whole myriad of remarkable
所有的工作开始的技术。
technologies that get
all that work started.
但同时在 JavaScript 中返回一个小对象,
But it also simultaneously in
JavaScript returns out a little object,
它叫做 promise 对象，只是一个普通的 JavaScript 对象。
that's gonna be called a promise object,
that is just a regular JavaScript object.
但有一些小的奖金功能，它一点奖金属性两，我们要去
But has some little bonus features on it
a little bonus properties two we're gonna
看看他们，看看他们一会儿是怎么玩的。
see them and
how they play out in a moment.